I just wanted
to live.
I just wanted to live.
But God,
God is unfair to me.
I have been living carefully with illness.
My only wish was to get a good medicine
for a body that can walk freely.
Later, I learned
that Liang Mountain has good medicine.
I was full of expectations.
Waiting for Liangshan people to come to Dongjing,
I took great pains
to follow you into the dark den of Yunxiang Pavilion
and fight against the Imperial City Department.
I wholeheartedly advised you.
Zhu'er even lost her life for this.
But in the end, you tell me
it's all too late.
My body couldn't wait any longer.
I won't survive.
And what about you?
The Emperor is absurd,
wanting to marry me off to a sixty-year-old man.
The whole Zhao family
is waiting to use me to advance their official careers.
The dismissal and reinstatement of court officials are treated like a trifling game.
The Emperor deserves to die.
The Zhao family deserves to die too.
They all deserve to die.
Han'er.
The Zhao family.
What happened to the Zhao Residence?
The Zhao Residence.
Naturally, it was completely destroyed.
Where are my sister-in-law and sister?
Your sister-in-law and sister?
How can I trouble Lady Zhao to pour tea herself?
My sister-in-law made sweet dumplings for me herself.
She deserves this tea.
Sister Xiaolian did, too.
Sister-in-law.
Sorry to trouble you, Lady Zhao.
Haven't you been looking for the medicine,
working so hard?
I merely...
took the Taoist priest's elixir...
I added a few rare poisons
and served it to them.
By the way.
When I left the mansion,
were they sleeping
peacefully?
Don't go.
It's useless.
How do you think
those knife sellers got in?
I made a deal with them.
I had them
pour oil all over
the Zhao Manor.
Tonight,
the moment the whole of Dongjing lights up,
the Zhao Manor
should be burning.
Let's go together
and be buried with Zhu'er.
Take them down.
Are you sure you want to leave?
Yes.
If you ever return to Dongjing,
need anything,
want a job,
or anything else,
just come to me.
You just need to ask.
I will grant any request.
Thank you for your care, Lord Duzhi.
Thank you
for finding his daughter for him.
Where are we going?
On such a beautiful day.
The world is vast.
We can go anywhere.
From now on,
I'll call you Brother Qisi.